People in business often make decisions based on their own personal feelings or instincts.
商界人士常常依据个人的感受或直觉做出决策。
It is quite horrifying to see people being guided by some unknown force.
看到人们受某种未知力量的引导，相当令人恐惧。
But how wise is it, really, to let your instincts drive your decisions?
但说真的，让直觉主导你的决策，到底有多明智呢？
In the decision-making process, relying on instincts only makes sense when you have vast experience to support you.
在决策过程中，只有当你有丰富的经验作支撑时，依靠直觉才说得通。
Simply “feeling” that something is right or should be done is highly subjective and can drown you.
仅仅“感觉”某件事是对的或应该做，是非常主观的，还可能让你遭遇灭顶之灾。
On the other hand, there is a more rational approach to making decisions.
另一方面，做决策还有一种更理性的方法。
Data and analysis have long been associated with informed decisions.
长期以来，数据和分析一直与有依据的决策联系在一起。
These reduce the likelihood of errors and increase the chances of success.
它们能降低出错的可能性，增加成功的机会。
Big, systematic data is the foundation of most of our decisions, personal and business alike.
大规模、系统化的数据是我们大多数决策的基础，个人决策和商业决策都是如此。
But with its extreme usability comes a complication: what do you do if you strongly feel something should not be done, even if the data insists that it should?
但数据极其好用，随之而来的却是一个难题：如果你强烈感到某件事不该做，即使数据明确表明应该做，你又该怎么办？
This seemingly easy question is what drives the need to understand the relationship between instincts and data in the decision-making process.
正是这个看似简单的问题，使人们有必要理解决策过程中直觉与数据之间的关系。
To put it simply, the solution to this dilemma is using data and instincts in conjunction to arrive at the best possible decisions.
简而言之，解决这个两难困境的办法，就是把数据和直觉结合起来使用，从而做出尽可能好的决策。
Instinctive decisions are always backed by previous experiences or information, which shows that instinctive decisions have worked in the past.
直觉决策总是以过往的经历或信息为依据，而这些经历或信息表明，直觉决策在过去是行之有效的。
Decisions are not about making the choice and braving the consequences because you want to blindly trust your instincts.
决策并不是说，因为你想盲目相信自己的直觉，就做出选择、直面后果。
They are about combining your inner wisdom with the knowledge of systematic data to make the best decisions.
决策在于把你内在的智慧与系统化数据所提供的知识结合起来，从而做出最好的决定。
In certain situations, rational analysis and data are impractical to employ.
在某些情况下，运用理性分析和数据是不现实的。
Absence of definitive criteria, time and resource constraints, and novel situations are instances which limit the practicality of data.
缺乏明确的标准、受到时间和资源的限制、面对从未遇到过的情况，这些都是限制数据实用性的例子。
The only feasible option is to rely on what your instincts tell you.
唯一可行的选择，就是依靠直觉告诉你的东西。
In these situations, instincts can help you make effective and quick decisions.
在这些情况下，直觉能帮助你做出有效而迅速的决策。
Combining instinctive and rational analysis produces well-rounded decisions.
将直觉分析与理性分析结合起来，能带来全面周到的决策。
It reduces the chances of making mistakes, and has increasingly become a favorite approach to decision-making among leaders of today.
这种做法能降低犯错的几率，并已日益成为当今领导者青睐的一种决策方法。